Hugh 听着 我呃 我喜欢你
Hugh, look, I, uh, I like you.
显而易见 我的意思是 这
Obviously. I mean, it's...
是我有时和你做爱的原因
why I keep having sex with you sometimes.
但 嗯 我想说 我们已经讨论过这些了
But, um, I mean, we've talked about this.
我有个女儿 我们一起工作
I have a daughter and we work together
只是 不会
and it's just... it wouldn't...
噢 Hugh 又来 是吗
Oh, Hugh, again, really?
噢
Oh.
嘿 Michael
Hey, Michael.
嘿 不好意思打扰你工作了
Hey. Sorry to bother you at work.
听着 你觉得我们可以和Lois交换过周末吗
Listen, do you think we can swap weekends with Lois?
啊 当然
Uh, yeah.
她和Mila周六约了一起玩
She has a play date with Mila on Saturday,
但是也许我可以让她换一天 为什么 怎么了
but I can probably move it. Why, what's up?
Ethan帮我们拿到了舞马的票
Ethan got us tickets to "Cavalia:
阿拉伯马群体验
The Arabian Horse Experience."
你在逗我吗
Are you kidding me?
Michael 那些票好像要上千美元
Michael, those tickets are like $1,000.
当然 而且还远不止上千
Yeah, they're a lot more than that
如果你还要看完舞马之后
if you want to meet the horses after,
接触马的话 -好恶心
- which we're gonna do. - It's gross!
他在努力成为超级继父
He's trying to be like this super stepdad
还给她买了喜欢的东西 非常烂俗
and buy her affection and it's tacky.
-是Rachel吗 -刚刚是Ethan吗
- Is that Rachel? - Was that Ethan?
他说什么了 我听到了我名字
What'd he say? I heard my name.
他只是说 是Rachel吗
He literally said, "Is that Rachel?"
-那是什么意思 -没什么
- What's that supposed to mean? - Nothing.
他送对钻石耳环给Lois
He got Lois diamond earrings
作为她的生日礼物 Michael 真正的钻石耳环哦
for her birthday, Michael.Real diamond earrings.
-我都没有真的钻石耳环 -真悲伤
- I don't have real diamond earrings. - That's just sad.
你是个成熟女性
You're a grown woman.
你应该有一些钻石耳环是的
You should have some real diamond earrings.
也许我该嫁给一个有钱的好莱坞同性恋经纪人
Maybe I'll marry a rich, gay Hollywood agent
-然后他就会给我买一对 -好吧 Rachel
- and he'll buy me a pair. - Okay, Rachel,
有这些钱并不容易
having all this money is not easy.
我甚至不能板着脸说
I can't even say it with a straight face.
钱使每件事都变得很简单
It makes everything weirdly easy.
噢 所以你周六的时候可以带Lois来吗
Oh, so can you bring Lois Saturday?
啊
Ugh.
-什么 -她在刁难你吗
- What? - Is she being difficult?
-什么 她是不是不想来 -Ethan
- What, she doesn't want to drive here?  - Ethan.
-是不是风太大了 -停
- Is it too windy?  - Stop.
她还是害怕好莱坞露天剧场吗
Is she still afraid of The Hollywood Bowl?
-只是 -好吧
- Just... - Uh, yes.
嗯 周六我肯定带上她 没问题
Um, Saturday I will definitely bring her, no problem.
顺便说下 告诉Ethan 我不是唯一一个害怕好莱坞露天剧场的人
And by the way, tell Ethan that I'm not the only one afraid of The Hollywood Bowl.
很多人都怕好莱坞露天剧场
Lots of people are afraid of The Hollywood Bowl
因为它是个噩梦
'cause it is a nightmare.
-每个人都怕 -不用了 我听到了 非常尖锐
- Everybody's afraid of the... - No, I heard her. It was screechy.
加油 再低点 各位
Push! Come on, lower, people!
-Larry 你好了没 -还没
-Larry, you almost done? - No.
好吧 还记得我跟你说过加入马球俱乐部的想法吗
Okay, remember I brought up the idea about joining a racquet club?
我们能不能晚些再讨论
Can we talk about this later, please?
今天我和那边的人聊过了
I talked to somebody there today
他们说现在加入正好
and they said now is the time to join.
现在都夏末了 价格更优惠
It's the end of summer. Rates are lower.
-能不加入吗 -只是天气很热而他们那有游泳池
- Can we not? - It's just so hot and they have a pool
还给小孩子设有专门的的区域
and the kids are so cooped up.
而且还有健身房
And they've got a great gym.
我们不打算加入马球俱乐部
We're not joining the racquet club.
我们没那么多钱
We don't have enough money.
这个我们等会再讨论
We'll talk about this later.
噢 Jack发热了 你能陪他一会吗在我送Elliot去学校这段时间
Oh, and Jack has a fever. Could you stay with him while I take Elliot to school?
不能 我和Ben Falcone有个早会要开
I can't! I have a breakfast meeting with Ben Falcone.
抱歉之前翻译的错误 以后Mr. First Lady都译为《第一男夫人》
-关于《第一男夫人》的吗 -不是 是别的事
- About "Mr. First Lady"? - No, this is a different thing.
-跟Hugh和Rachel一起 -不 不是和他们
- With Hugh and Rachel? - No, it's not with Hugh and Rachel.
-爸爸 -我没和他们做任何事
- Daddy! - I don't do everything with them.
-陪我玩 -噢 亲爱的 Jack
- Play with me. - Oh, honey, Jack.
去找妈妈 好吧 我的毛孔已打开
Go to Mommy, please. My pores are open,
对细菌特别敏感
I'm very susceptible to germs.
来这 Jack 来妈妈这里 亲爱的
Come on, Jack. Come to Mommy, honey.
噢 亲爱的 你能带着他吗
Oh, honey, can you take him, please?
我爱你但我不能抱你
I love you but I can't hug you.
Jack 来妈妈这
Jack, come to Mommy!
-噢 我的天 我非常 -算了
- Oh, my God, I'm so... - Forget it.
您的呼叫已被转到
Your call has been forwarded
自动语音留言系统
to an automatic voice-message system.
818-25
818-25...
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
你刚在打篮球吗
Were you playing basketball?
-什么 -Larry在哪
- What? - Where's Larry?
不知道
I don't know.
好吧 Ben那边有消息吗 他看过我们的剧本吗
Well, have you heard from Ben? Has he read our script.
我想说 太不可思议了 看一个剧本
I mean, this is crazy.It shouldn't take someone
根本不需要占用那么长时间 呃 好吗
that long to read a script. It's like, hello,
-Ben看完剧本前什么事都做不了 是吗 -Rachel
- nothing can happen till Ben reads the script, right? - Rachel.
- 他是奶酪 她是老鼠 -Rachel
- He's the cheese, she's the rat. - Rachel.
好吧 苍蝇不叮无缝的蛋
Okay, the rat can't eat if there's no cheese.
他好像不明白 -Rachel 怎么了
It's like he's not understanding... -Rachel, what is going on?
我醒来的时候你就已经走了
I wake up, you're gone,
然后我给你打了六次电话 你居然都没接
and then I call you six times, you don't pick up your phone?
你想谈谈吗 -我
Do you want to talk? -I...
我是说 我甚至不知道我们会
I mean, I don't even know what we would...
谈论什么 呃
talk about. I mean...
那么 上次这种事发生的时候
How about, the last time this happened,
你说过 不会有下一次
you said, "never again."
是的 -然后昨天晚上 突然间地
Right. -And then last night out of nowhere,
你就扑向我
you threw yourself at me...
哇 哇 哇偶 我扑向了你
Wh-Wh-whoa. Threw myself at you.
是啊 -你说什么呢
Yeah. -What are you talking about?
Hugh 我是喝得太多了 好吗
Hugh, I had too much to drink, okay?
酒后乱性了
I made a bad decision.
这就是为什么人们常说说 不要喝太多酒 对吧
That's why people say, don't have so much to drink, right?
所以我会不再喝多了
So I won't drink so much anymore.
这种事不会再发生了 我们再也不用谈论它了
This won't happen again, we never have to talk about it again.
永远不要喝酒 不要酒后乱性 不要醉后谈论
Never drink, never make a bad decision, never talk.
三大点
The big three.
发生了什么事 怎么了
What happened? What's going on?
你们太奇怪了
You guys are being weird.
你生我的气吗 你为什么生我的气
You're mad at me? Why are you mad at me?
你们总是迟到 我不需要你们来谴责我
You guys are late all the time, I don't need the firing squad
因为我比平时晚一点
because I'm a little later than normal, all right?
好吧 我去了贝弗利山庄吃早餐
Fine, I went to Beverly Hills for breakfast.
这就是你们要答案
There you go.
你为什么要去] 贝弗利山庄吃早餐
Why would you go to Beverly Hills for breakfast?
那里有很棒的餐厅 所以我
They have great restaurants that I...
我在那里吃早饭啊
and I eat breakfast there.
你和谁吃的早饭
Who'd you have breakfast with?
和我自己
It was just me.
为什么我们干嘛要谈论
Why are we even talking about every thing
这些我们生活中无聊的琐事
that happens in each of our lives?
因为我们不需要  -你跟Ben谈过了吗
'Cause we do not have to do that. -Have you talked to Ben?
就今天早上 我和Ben吃早餐了
Like, this morning. Did I have breakfast with Ben?
等等 你是和Ben吃的早餐 -对呀
Wait, you had breakfast with Ben? -Yeah!
为了我们的电影 -我们都还没有提到过它
About our movie? -We didn't even talk about it.
你是和Ben Falcone一起吃的早饭
You had breakfast with Ben Falcone
然后你们都没有说起过我们的电影
and you did not talk about our movie?
这是另一回事
This was about a different thing.
什么另一件事
What different thing?
跟你无关 那不是
It doesn't involve you. This is not...
我们不需要
We don't have to...
够了
It's too much.
淡定 好吗 谢谢你了
Back off, all right? Thank you.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我需要吃点东西 行吗
I need to eat something. Is that okay?
我和Ben早饭的时候什么都没吃
I didn't eat anything at my breakfast with Ben.
那的东西都好贵啊
Everything was so expensive.
我都不知道谁要买单
I didn't know who was gonna pay for it.
打死也不去贝弗利山庄吃早饭了
Never eat breakfast in Beverly Hills.
你和Ben见面干嘛
What were you meeting Ben for?
为了我的真人秀
My reality show idea.
喜剧小品版的《美国偶像》吗
That "American Idol" sketch comedy thing
赢的人可以上《周六夜现场》
where the winner goes on "Saturday Night Live,"
这永远不会发生
a thing that can never happen
因为你没有合法的联系
because you have no legal connection
不管是《周六夜现场》还是《美国偶像》
to either "Saturday Night Live" or "American Idol."
是的 我很清楚
Yes, I'm very aware of that.
这就是为什么我想要找个名人
That's why I'm trying to get a celebrity attached
来推销它
to try to help sell it,
所以我问Ben 他是否会让Melissa参与进来
so I asked Ben if he'd get Melissa involved.
我的天 -什么鬼
Oh, my God! -What?!
什么什么鬼
What?!
无名之辈.
Larry 我们需要请Ben和Melissa来演《第一男夫人》
Larry, we need Ben and Melissa for "Mr. First Lady,"
翻译：Amy Ariel
而不是你那和我们无关的愚蠢真人秀
not your stupid reality show that we're not even a part of.
那就是你生气的原因吗
Is that why you're mad?
翻译：天天天 Echo
就因为没搭上你们一起
Because you're not involved?
我们是结婚了吗 就不能
What are we, married and not allowed
翻译：Nana 叫你一声美人
被允许做自己的事吗
to do anything on our own?
这是一个邪教吗
This is a cult?
你能把太阳镜拿掉吗
Could you take those sunglasses off?
当然可以 只要你们别那么烦躁
Sure. As soon as you guys take your bad moods off.
校对：DAWN
后期：大 颖
开心了吧
Happy?
压制：老司机
这不是我的球
This is not my ball.
是Hugh的蠢球 -我才不想要那个该死的球
It's Hugh's stupid ball! -I don't want the damn ball!
噢 -哇
Whoa! -Aah!
早上好 大家
Morning, team.
卧槽 什么鬼 什么时候搞的
Holy crackers, when did this happen?
噢
Oh.
一定是一只鸟或者
That must have been a bird or...
可怜的小家伙
Poor little guy.
好吧 我就是想来个突袭 看看事情进展的怎么样
Well, just wanted to pop in, see how things are going,
看看写到哪了
see how the writing's coming.
呃 快完成了
Uh... we're almost done.
很好 很好 Connie会很开心的
Good, good. Connie will like that.
在这世上我最喜欢的事就是
And I know my favorite thing in the world
坐在那 手里拿着一袋奇多
is sitting back with a bag of Cheetos
读一本刚出炉的《放屁人》剧本
reading a fresh "Fartlemans" script.
真的吗
Really?
嘿Tamara
Hey, Tamara!
你能不能打个电话 问问窗户的报价
Can you call around and get some quotes on some windows?
呃 事实上 我们才写了4页
Uh, actually, we're on page four,
还早着呢 你个白痴
so not almost done, you psycho.
我又不知道他会这样说
I didn't know that was gonna happen!
好吧 你知道吗 木已成舟
All right, you know what? What's done is done.
所以 有人告诉Ben了吗 他有读过我们的剧本了吗
So... has anyone talked to Ben? Has he read our script?
你现在是认真的吗
Are you serious right now?
吃早饭的时候你怎么不问他
Why didn't you ask him at breakfast
反而谈你愚蠢的附带项目
instead of talking about your dumb side project?
我们又没结婚
We're not married.
我们可以做其他的事情
We're allowed to do other things.
呃
Uhh.
你知道吗
You know what?
我要在我车里吃午饭
I'm gonna eat my lunch in my car.
那你不是好棒棒
Good!
简直有毒
Well, this is toxic.
你真的不打算告诉我们咱要在这里做什么吗
Are you seriously not gonna tell us what we're doing down here?
我已经告诉过你们
I already told you,
当你们需要知道的时候我会说的
I'll tell you when you need to know.
嗯
Um... tch-tch-tch-tch.
美容牙科
Cosmetic dentistry.
你觉得我需要镶牙
You think I need veneers
因为我牙缝大
'cause I have giant gaps in my teeth?
嗯 镶个牙又不会怎么了
Well, veneers wouldn't kill you.
呃 哦 呃 402
Uh, oh, uh, 402.
治疗和咨询
Therapy and counseling?
讲真 你要带我们去看心理治疗师
Seriously, you're taking us to a therapist?
我才不要看心理治疗师 疯了吧
I'm not gonna see a therapist. This is insane.
我不觉得这事有什么
I don't think it's insane.
我是说 运动团队也去看心理治疗师而我们就是个团队
I mean, sports teams see therapists and we're a team.
我们是个有一堆大问题的团队
We're a team that has massive problems.
不是一堆问题 是一个问题 你就是那个问题
Not problems, problem. You are the problem.
真正的问题是 Ben Falcone得花多久才能读完剧本
The real problem is how long does it take Ben Falcone to read a script?
说真的 他是不是不识字啊 我很认真地在问这个问题哦
I mean, is he illiterate? I'm seriously asking that question.
真是简直了 我是说 他也没回我呢
It's absolutely crazy. I mean, he hasn't gotten back to me about my thing either.
我的天 你开玩笑吗
Oh, my God. Are you kidding?
你知道吗 我很高兴我们在这看心理治疗师
You know what? I'm glad we're here seeing a therapist
因为我需要有人跟我解释
'cause I need someone to explain to me
你为什么这么疯
why you are so insane.
火气真大
So much anger.
治疗费用记在你保险上 对吧
This is going on your insurance, right?
这到底是什么鬼
What the hell is that?
哦 得了吧 你从来没见过那个吗
Oh, come on. You've never seen that?
你按个按钮 他办公室里的提示灯就亮了
You press the button, a light goes on in his office
告诉他我们到了
and tells him we're here.
难道在明确的时间预约好
Because having an appointment at a specific time
还不足以安排好这个吗
is not enough to coordinate all this?
预约在其他行业都管用 但这些人
It works for all other businesses, but these people...
这只在你买它账的时候才管用
This is only gonna work if you buy into it.
你这是引用Jim Jones的话
That's a Jim Jones quote.
他是达拉斯牛仔队的教练吗
Is that the coach of the Dallas Cowboys?
不 你说的是Jerry Jones 他是达拉斯牛仔队的所有者
No, that's Jerry Jones and he's the owner of the Dallas Cowboys.
Jim Jones是那个说服了一群人
Jim Jones is a man who convinced a bunch of people
在法属盖亚那自杀的人
to kill themselves in French Guyana.
我有点紧张 你觉得我有时间去撒尿吗
I just got nervous. Do you think I have time to pee?
我要去尿尿
I'm gonna go pee.
Rachel 我们谈谈
Rachel, let's talk.
真的假的 你宁愿要读"美味"杂志
Really? You're gonna read "Saveur" magazine
而不是谈谈我们的事
rather than talk about us?
我们不是因为我俩的事来的 好吗
We're not here because of us, okay?
我们来是为了工作
We're here because of work.
所以我们到此为止吧别争论了
So let's just leave it at that.
每次我们睡了之后你就这样
This always happens to you when we sleep together.
你崩溃了 绝口不提 然后我们就不谈了
You freak out, shut down and won't talk.
”每次“ 这听起来就好像我们睡过好多次一样
"Always happens"? That makes it sound like we've slept together tons of times.
我们就睡过三次
We've slept together three times.
我们睡过四次
We slept together four times.
三次
Three.
还有在停车场楼梯那次
The staircase in that parking garage.
哦 是哦
Oh... Kay.
我没算那次 但是
I didn't count that, but...
你为什么不算那次
Why would you not count it?
我没
I didn't...
算进去
... count it.
Larry 我注意到你盯着我的鞋看
Larry, I couldn't help but notice you staring at my shoes.
嗯
Hmm?
我穿这个是因为我营救被抛弃的长臂猿
I wear them because I rescue abandoned gibbon monkeys.
你选择了坐椅子 有意思
It's interesting that you took the chair.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗯 这无关好坏 只是个信息
Well, it's not good or bad, it's just information.
在多角恋中 很多情况下
Many times in a polyamorous relationship,
那个占主导地位的成员会单独行动
the more dominant member will individuate
把自己和另外两个爱人区分开来
and set himself apart from the other two lovers.
哦 -不是的 不是这回事
- Oh... - No, no, that's not what's happening.
是的 我们没有
Yeah, we're not...
我们就是一起工作而已
We just work together.
我们是朋友 仅此而已
And we're friends. That's it.
好吧 不论Larry是不是主导着
Well, whether Larry is having sex
他和你们两人的性交
with both of you in a dominant way...
不是 他没有
No, he's not.
但这事情怎么看都和性有关
But it seems like something sexual is going on.
我绝对是感受到了性能量
I'm definitely picking up on a sexual energy.
我们没有 所以
We're not. So...
我们是个写作团队
We're a writing team.
哦 再说一次 不管这事是不是和性有关
Oh. Again, whether it's sexual,
不管你们是不是想要这事变得和性有关 都没关系
whether you want it to be sexual, it doesn't matter.
所有的关系本质上都是建立在
All relationships are essentially built
公开真诚的交流基础之上的
on open, honest communication.
就好比是婚姻或是三角家庭
Just like a marriage or a ménage à trois.
现在 Rachel 你在电话里说
Now, Rachel, on the phone,
你们在为节目合作这事上
you said that you were having trouble
遇到点问题
working together on your show.
什么节目
What show is that?
一个叫《放屁人》的卡通
"The Fartlemans" It's a cartoon.
我知道《放屁人》这是我最喜欢的节目之一
I know "The Fartlemans." It's one of my favorite shows.
哦 哇 你孩子多大了
Oh, wow. How old are your kids?
哦 我没有小孩
Oh, I don't have children.
现在 Rachel 你在电话上提到过
Now, Rachel, you mentioned that the issue
似乎和彼此之间的信任问题
seemed to be one of trust.
这就是你说的 信任问题
That's what you said? Trust?
这是关于隐私界限问题
It's boundary issues.
Kaine医生
Dr. Kaine...
本字幕由Ciassic字幕组提供，仅供试看之用，禁止用于任何商业行为，若因私自散布造成法律问题，Classic字幕组恕不负责。
我可不是什么医生
I'm not a doctor.
Kaine先生
Mr. Kaine,
我做了没什么错的事情
I did something very innocent.
但是这俩人
And then these guys,
为此攻击我
they attack me for it.
因为你做了件极其荒唐的蠢事
Because you did something monstrously stupid.
他们现在就在那攻击我呢
That's the attack right there.
这种骂人 完全是没有必要的
It's the name calling, which is completely unnecessary.
然后每个人都需要做点妥协
And everyone just needs to back off.
- 那些人算是每个人 -他们
- Who is everyone? - Them.
- Rachel 和 Hugh  - Rachel 和 Hugh
- Rachel and Hugh? - Rachel and Hugh.
很好 我们定义了每个人
Great. We've defined that.
所以 Rachel 和 Hugh
So, Rachel and Hugh...
还有我的老婆和小孩
And my wife and my kids.
每个人都想要点什么
And it's just everyone wants something
但是我让他们失望了
and then I just let them down.
我想做点什么 但是都还远远不够
I try to do something and it's never enough.
但是这是其他事情了
But that's a separate thing.
这是别的事 这不是为什么我们在这里的原因
And that's another... That's not why we're here.
我们在这里的原因是他们
Why we're here is because of them
这就是要解决的事情 这俩人
and that's the issue, these people.
你现在可以问他们一个问题了
You can ask them a question now
-因为你刚刚问了我一个问题 -对
- 'cause you asked me a question. - Right.
- 然后我回答了你的问题 -嗯哼
- And I answered the question.- Mm-hmm.
-我到这就够了 -嗯哼
- And that was my end of the bargain.- Mm-hmm.
现在到他们了
And now it's their end of the bargain
因为该轮到他们了
because it's their turn.
很好
Great.
Rachel 我从你开始问
Rachel, I'll start with you...
你知道为什么我现在这么抓狂
Do you want to know what makes me so mad?!
在你眼前的这两个人 是我一生中
These two people right here are the most selfish people
遇见的最自私的人
I have ever met in my entire life.
他们俩没一个人会愿意说
Have either of them ever bothered to say,
嗨 Larry 你一定过的很艰难吧
hey, Larry, yeah, it must be tough for you
作为唯一一个家庭支柱
to be the sole provider for a wife
老婆想要一个游泳池
who wants a pool and two kids
两个小孩又经常生病 情况糟糕时
who are always getting sick and if things go bad,
我得打电话给Jen的爸爸 因为她不愿意
I have to call Jen's dad because she doesn't do it
即使那是她的爸爸 但是我是打电话的那个人
even though it's her father, so I'm the one that's gotta do it,
这样其实毫无道理可言 只是因为她和这个男人
which makes absolutely no sense,'cause she's had a relationship
认识了一辈子
with this man for her entire life
我 我们之间摩擦很多
and I... We have a very frictiony relationship and that's...
但那也是我心甘情愿结的婚
I'd love to get into that one.
所以我就得当那个打电话的人
So, I'm the one who had to call up and say,
然后说 嗨Curtis 没什么事
hey, Curtis, this is not a big deal.
其实这也没什么大不了的
This is just a no-big-deal conversation.
我是个娶了你女儿的穷小子
I'm the guy that married your daughter
即使我也负担不起她的生活
even though I can't seem to support her,
但我能跟你借32000美金吗
but can I borrow $32,000
因为家里前院的树长了个霉菌
because we have a tree in the front yard that has a fungus
那个专业人士说霉菌随时都会掉到我们房子里
and the guy said that it can fall on our house at any moment
或者掉到邻居家
or it can fall on a neighbor's house,
那也很惨因为我得赔钱
which is just as bad because I'd have to pay for that.
我不但有生病的小孩 现在还有生病的树
I have sick kids and now I have a sick tree.
我真的有很大压力
It's a lot of pressure on me,
所以我不会对这俩人感到抱歉
so I'm very sorry if these people,
他们没有和我一样有那么多同时需要处理的急事
they don't need as much irons in the fire as I do
因为我不能只靠《第一男夫人》播出
because I can't rely on "Mr. First Lady" happening,
因为《第一男夫人》可能根本播出不了
because guess what. "Mr. First Lady's" probably not gonna happen
因为Ben Falcone 太懒太蠢根本不会去读它
because Ben Falcone is too lazy and too stupid to read it.
不好意思 你本来要问他们问题的
I'm sorry, you were about to ask them a question.
我才知道轮到谁了
So, I know whose turn it is now.
好吧 我觉得在你说了这么多以后
Well, I would think after all of that, Larry,
Larry 下一个还应该是你
it would be anybody's turn but yours.
Rachel 你呢
Rachel? You?
你有什么愿意和Larry分享的
Is there anything that you would like to share with Larry
那些他不知道的事
that he doesn't know about?
没有
No.
好 Hugh
Okay. Hugh?
没有 嗯 我们只是
No. Um, we're just...
三个人一起工作
three people that work together and...
我们之间没有性关系
none of us are having sex with each other.
我总感觉这里有关于性关系的冲突
I feel like there's a sexual tension somewhere in here.
我也不觉得
And I don't think it's...
这来源于我
I don't think it's coming from me.
虽然我也不是很能确定
Although I can't be sure.
这一路上车子里真是安静啊
That was kind of a quiet car ride.
是以为我说你们俩自私
Was it because I called you guys selfish?
所以你们对我生气了
You're mad at me because I said
就因为说你们是我见过最自私的人
you're the most selfish people I ever met?
Larry 没人生你的气
No one's mad at you, Larzy.
我觉得我们确实是忘记了
I do think that we forget
你现在经济情况很紧张
that you're under a lot of financial pressures.
做小孩生意的好处就是
Good thing about being in the kids business
这是唯一一个在娱乐产业里安稳的工作了
is it's the only steady work in the entertainment industry.
这样我是为什么小孩生意不被认为
Which, of course, is why it's not considered
是娱乐产业的一部分了
part of the entertainment industry.
我们被炒鱿鱼了
We're getting fired?
我不这么认为 但我也不知道
I don't think so, but I don't know.
我不知道我们超出预算那么多了
I do know that we are way over budget.
我以为你刚刚和我们说
I thought you just told us
我们是第一名的
that we're number one...
-在和二到几的男孩子里   -对 -对
- ... with boys two to...- Yeah. - Yeah.
-二到六 -二到六
- Two to six.- ... two to six.
相信我 我和Connie说过了
And believe me, I brought that up to Connie.
但是你们没有在截止日期内完成 我们的经费在燃烧啊
When you guys miss your deadlines, it costs us money.
那可是Connie最在意的事了
And that's all that Connie cares about.
但我起码知道她正打算
But I do know she's talking about going
从你们中开除掉一个 我不知道
from three writers to two. I don't know.
-那是什么意思啊   -我们该怎么办啊
- What does that mean? - What can we do?
从短期来看 你们得快点补上你们得剧本
In the short-term, you guys have to catch up on these scripts.
-好 –可以 可以
- Yes. - Fine, fine.
从长远地来看 也许应该好好考虑一下
And in the long-term, maybe think about who you lose,
真的发生时 谁要离开
should it come to that.
我的意思是 你不能退出 你是智商担当
I mean, you can't lose you. He's the brains.
然后Rachel可以写女性角色那部分
And Rachel writes all the girl parts.
剩下Larry
And Larry...
我想不出Larry可以做什么
I don't know what Larry does.
所以 我直觉告诉我Larry可以退出
So my gut says lose Larry.
噢 那很诱人啊
Oh, that's attractive.
哦 让我们快点完成剧本吧
Oh, let's get to it.
呃 Skippy Fartleman和屁屁校长留堂
Ah... Skippy Fartleman was in detention with Principal Butts.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
我正在写信给Ben
I'm writing Ben.
我不能再等了
I can't wait anymore.
你有那么忙吗 Ben 真的假的
Are you that busy, Ben? Really?
你刚才有听到Allen说的那些话吗
Did you hear anything that Allen just said?
呃 我听到了 Hugh 我听到的是
Uh, yes, I did, Hugh, and what I heard
这些工作并不像你说的那么稳定
was that these jobs are not as stable as you said.
好吧 所以现在 你就只玩在你自己手上的球喽
Well, so now you're just taking your balls into your own hands?
什么
What?
没有这种说法啊
That is not an expression.
好吧
Well...
Ben Falcone
Ben Falcone.
嘿Ben 你在同Rachel Hugh 还有 Larry通话中
Hey, Ben, you're on speaker with Rachel, Hugh and Larry.
嘿 伙计们 我很抱歉过了这么久才来联系你们
Hey, gang, sorry it took me so long to get back to you.
没事 没事 慢慢来
No, no, no, no. Take your time.
-感觉很快啊  -好的 第一件事哈
- It seemed fast. - Well, first things first.
我不得不说 我真是笑疯了
I just have to say I laughed my itty-bitty nuts off
看了你们电影剧本的时候
reading your movie.
你们写得太有意思了
It's so funny, you guys.
-噢 –噢 –谢谢Benji
- Oh. - Oh. - Thanks, Benji.
我是有一个想法啦
I do have one thought, though.
如果你们要是觉得太疯狂了就告诉我
Tell me if you think this is too crazy,
但要是Melissa来扮演总统的角色怎么样
but what if Melissa plays the role of the president.
人呢
Guys?
-你们还在那吗  -呃 是的
- Are you there? - Uh, yeah.
呃 恩 Melissa McCarthy来扮演总统
Uh, hmm, Melissa McCarthy as the president.
嗯 很有趣 呃
Hmm, interesting. Um...
要不算了 可能会有点奇怪
Or not. I mean, it might be weird.
我只是想 也许这会让你们得作品锦上添花的
I just sort of thought maybe it would help it get made
而且这会很有趣的 但是 呃
and it might be fun, but, um,
也要你们觉得她适合这个角色才行
if you don't think she's right for the role...
别别别 就Melissa了 很好
No, no, no. Yes, yes on Melissa.
这个想法棒极了 完美
Great idea, perfect idea.
-是的 Melissa –嗯嗯 很好
- Yay Melissa! - Okay, great.
好的 到时候我会你们这群小坏蛋回卡通镇的
Well, I will let you ding dongs get back to cartoon town.
哦 嘿 Ben 耽误一会
Oh, hey, Ben, real quick.
呃 呃 我是Larry
Um, um, this is Larry here.
恩 我知道 我认得你的声音啦
Yeah, I know. I recognize your voice, bud.
呃 只是 呃 我想试着问你一下
Uh, just, uh, wanted to take your temperature
之前我们谈论过的 关于我的真人秀的想法
about my reality show idea that we talked about before.
噢
Oh.
那个节目超冷的啊 兄弟
That's like ice cold, buddy.
啊 哈
Uh-huh.
像冰冷的尸体 毫无生机
That's like a dead body.
好的 好的 我明白你的意思了
Yeah, yeah, got it, okay.
呃 好了 各位再见了
Um, all right. Bye, gangers.
拜拜
Bye.
看来他并不想要轻松地赚到百万美金啊
He doesn't want an easy million bucks,
他不想轻松地赚到百万美金啊
he doesn't want an easy million bucks.
但我们把Melissa拿下了
But we got Melissa!
你懂的
Girl.
Ben准备好了吗
Ben, you ready?
哦 我喜欢你的鞋子 我有一双一样的
Oh, I love your shoes. I have the same pair.
噢 谢谢
Oh, thank you.
我还有一双鞋 穿上刚好超出我膝盖一些
I have another pair that goes just above the knee.
随着Pooper走进狗狗屋
"As Pooper walks in the dog house,
我们就退幕
we fade out."
嗯
Mmm.
你真的会以为这些事情
You'd really think these things
会比较容易收尾的
would be easier to wrap.
我还是不敢相信 我们那疯狂的计划居然奏效了
I still can't believe that our insane plan is working
而且我们还即将迎来Melissa McCarthy
and we are maybe gonna get Melissa McCarthy
出现在我们的电影里
to be in our movie.
简直不敢相信啊
It's crazy.
我们要喝香槟吗
We're drinking the champagne?
等下 我以为我们要一直存着它
Wait, I thought we were saving that
直到事情真的定下来了
for when there was something official
就像我们要准备签合同了 或是什么的
like we were gonna sign contracts or something.
我没有要打开它
I'm not gonna open it.
我只是要我们大家花几秒钟感受一下
I just want us to take a moment
我们离成功有多近了
to realize how close we are to opening it.
我的意思是 我们已经
I mean, the three of us are very close
离一些我们都没有尝过的胜利滋味很近了
to drinking something none of us enjoys the taste of.
嗯哈
Mm-hmm.
现在 有谁想要熬夜
Now, who feels like staying late
然后敲出另一份《放屁人》剧本 我们可处于顺风顺水的时候
and knocking out another "Fartlemans" script? We're on a roll.
或是我们可以顺着走廊走 找到Connie再杀掉她 我都做好准备了
That or we can go down the hall and murder Connie. I'm up for either one.
我会的 但是我绝对会感到不舒服的
I would, but I am definitely getting sick.
而我有Lois 然后我的保姆有一些事我要去处理
And I have Lois and my nanny has something,
但我们可以明天再做
but we'll do it tomorrow.
你知道吗 我会做好自己那份的
You know what? I'll do one on my own.
-真的吗  -是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
更多冷门美影 英美剧 请关注 Classic字幕组的微博哦 字幕组等你来撩~
不 不 我们什么都在一起写
No, no, we write everything together.
啊哦 走
Uh-uh, go.
-你们有自己的生活和家庭 -我来吧
- You guys have got lives and families - I'll do it.
行 嗯 工作别太拼
Okay, well, don't work too hard.
但足够认真到可以做我们所有的工作就好
But work hard enough where you do all our work for us.
没问题 Lar
You got it, Lar.
Hugh
Hugh.
我只想谢谢你什么都没说出去
I just want to thank you for not saying anything,
你知道 当我们在
you know, when we were at the...
Blaine Kaine的办公室
Blaine Kaine's office.
受尊敬的非医生Blaine Kaine
The esteemed non-doctor Blaine Kaine.
只是我们一起工作而我有个孩子
It's just we work together and I have a kid and...
我懂
I get it.
真的
I do.
我是说 你有你的顾虑
I mean, you have your concerns.
我没有任何这些顾虑 但
I have none of those concerns, but...
我尊重你的顾虑
I respect your concerns.
所以我们没问题吧
So we're good?
是 我们没有问题
Yes, we're good.
我是说 我们身处一段多方关系
I mean, we're in a polyamorous relationship,
跟Larry Dorf 无性关系
nonsexual, with Larry Dorf.
那是我从小一直的梦想
That was always my dream growing up.
什么
What...
-你在干什么 -我在试着使眼色
- What are you doing?- I'm trying to wink.
那叫使眼色吗
That's winking?
我不知道怎么使眼色
I don't know how to wink.
呃 好吧
Uh, all right.
好 明天见
All right, I'll see you tomorrow.
好
All right.
“房内: 放屁人的树屋”
"Interior: Skippy Fartleman's tree house."